<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Running +</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="banner">ca-app-pub-6801991288885228/8239942792</string>
    <string name="admob_intestitial">ca-app-pub-6801991288885228/9716675991</string>

    
    
<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <!-- Programmme 1 -->
    <string name="title1">1. Run no farther or faster than you have to.</string>
    <string name="description1">In other words,strive for optimal training benefits with the least amount of work
    ...</string>
    <string name="fullText1"><![CDATA[
        In other words, strive for optimal training benefits with the least amount of work. This is the cardinal
        rule of Daniels"'"s training philosophy. As he likes to put it: "If I said that you could run a five-minute
        mile with one program that took 30 miles a week or another program that took 80 miles a week,
        which would you choose?" The answer"'"s a no-brainer, of course, but many runners nonetheless
        train too hard and too inefficiently. The outcome is worse performances, not better ones.
        Daniels tries to cut out the waste, maximizing improvement and minimizing injuries.
        A corollary to this rule: Whenever you do a workout, know what you"'"re trying to achieve.
        Is it endurance? Speed? Running economy? If you"'"re training intelligently, you"'"ll know the answer before you begin to sweat.]]>
    </string>


    <!-- Programmme 2 -->
    <string name="title2">2. Avoid injuries."\n"</string>
    <string name="description2">Duh. Who doesn"'"t pay homage to this old chestnut? But it"'"s easier said than done
    ...</string>
    <string name="fullText2">
       <![CDATA[ Duh. Who doesn"'"t pay homage to this old chestnut? But it"'"s easier said than done.
        To help you escape the trap of overuse injuries, Daniels offers the following formula:
        Stick with your current weekly mileage for at least three weeks. Then, if your training feels comfortable,
        you can increase your weekly mileage by the number of workouts you are running per week (that is to say,]]>
        if you"'"re doing four workouts, you can increase by four miles).
    </string>
    <!-- Programmme 3 -->
    <string name="title3">3. Pump up your stride rate to 180 per minute.</string>
    <string name="description3">At the 1984 Olympics, Daniels and his wife, Nancy, analyzed the stride frequencies of runners
    ...</string>
    <string name="fullText3">
        <![CDATA[At the 1984 Olympics, Daniels and his wife, Nancy, analyzed the stride frequencies of runners
        from 800 meters to the marathon. At distances from 5000 meters on up, the top runners,
        both men and women, were remarkably consistent: They ran with a stride rate of about 180 strides per minute.]]>
    </string>
    <!-- Programmme 4 -->
    <string name="title4">4. Run 75 to 80 percent of your weekly mileage at a relaxed pace.</string>
    <string name="description4">This kind of running builds your basic aerobic capacity, and strengthens the key running muscles
    ...</string>
    <string name="fullText4">
        <![CDATA[This kind of running builds your basic aerobic capacity, and strengthens the key running muscles,
        joints, and ligaments. Your EZ pace is equivalent to your 5-K race pace, plus 90 to 120 seconds per mile.
        (If you race 5-Ks at 8:00 pace, your EZ pace is 9:30 to 10:00.)]]>
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_location_">Location_Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gps_">Gps_Activity</string>
</resources>
